Hello friends, my name is Kabir. You are
watching my audition. After watching it, you must have
understood what topic we are going to talk about today.
If you have
financed your mobile from TVS Credit Finance and got it
insured, then keep watching till the end of this video.
If you are new to this channel, then
like and subscribe to the channel. So let's
start
how we do it. TVS Credit, the company which insures mobile, does it
with ICICI Lombard.
To register an ICICI Lombard claim, you must have
one of these things - policy number, mobile number. While registering a mobile number, only then you
can click. ICICI Lombard can be
intimated in two ways - by calling the customer care
and by visiting the ICSE board website. They will
tell you how to intimate a cashless claim in both ways. You can also see the customer care
number and the link to the official website of ICICI Lombard
in the description.
Yes,
while intimate a claim on call in ICICI Lombard, always keep in
mind that the first
question that will be asked to you is when did your phone break?  You have to
tell the time of breakage today, you
can tell anything and the second question will
ask you how your phone broke,
whatever incident happened with you and you
can tell that at the time of breakage or you can say I was going to
work at 9:00 this morning when someone on
Activa tried to overtake me,
he collided with me and I fell
and my phone got damaged in the pocket of my pants,
now you can say in this way
that if your phone got damaged then you
can say my phone fell out of the pocket and
fell in the water and after that you have to tell
a mobile number and your email ID and
your pick up bed rest, you have to pay the phone from here, you have to
tell that address, after that you will
immediately get a call on your email ID in
which your claim number will be there and the
date of payment will be there and in that you will
also get a link to pay ₹5000 which ICICI
Lombard courier charges, as soon as you
complete this process, win7 get your phone
repaired or you can get it by going to the
official website of ICICI Lombard
Intimate claim is easy, so
let's start like home, click on the link,
something like this will appear to you on the interface,
enter the phone number here
and click on submit,
after clicking on submit you will
see the interface like this, here you can describe the loss description of any
incident that happened to you, like if
your phone is broken,
you can describe it and here you have to
enter the loss deposit on the day
you are intimate the claim and the type of
loss, whatever your phone accident, alarm or
vitamin has happened, you will select it here
and here you will enter the address from
where your phone has to be picked up and
dropped
[Music]
I will enter the pin code and
select the state and city,
I will enter the email ID here which you are
using currently because as soon as
you submit it, you will immediately get a
mail receiver in which your claim number will be
mentioned, all the other details will
remain on your mail only,
I will enter a communication number here, there is no
need to enter this registered number  If not, you
can enter the publication number so that
if the company wants to contact you, they can
easily contact you.
And you can enter the mobile number in this chapter note. You
can enter the alarms decoration or simple accident alarms or
liquid chilli.
After clicking on this,
you will see options like this.
So keep in mind here, there is an
option given here, check clear to option for
investment in that do not switch to option
cashless service. If you
want a reimbursement service, then click here,
but we want cashless service, that is why we will
not click on it and click on submit.
Now, in
this way your claim has been submitted.
Here you can see your claim number.
This claim number will also be received on your email ID.
Guys, if your phone
goes into total loss, ICICI Lombard
deducts your depreciation and transfers whatever
amount is left to your account.
It has a small
process and some documents have to be uploaded.  You have to
upload a claim form
and the purchase bill of your mobile and
one of your ID proof, so how do you upload it, then
he tells you that
guys, to upload the document, first of all you will
click on the mobile and apply screen and track the claim, here
you have to enter the clearance number which
you have received on your mail ID and click on submit,
after clicking on this,
you will see an interface like this, here you
can also check the status of your claim
and by going here you will upload
whatever document you require,
claim form original in byes or
identity proof, whatever you have to upload, so in
this way you will apply
that guys, as soon as you click on upload,
after that whatever form of yours will be
submitted, so guys, as
soon as we complete the process of uploading this low claim, within
seven
days whatever amount you have will be
transferred to your account, if you found this video
useful, then like this video
and subscribe to the channel  Subscribe hmm thank you
[music]